{
  "round1": {
    "categories": [
      {
        "name": "Space",
        "questions": [
          {
            "value": 200,
            "question" : "What is the seventh planet in the solar system?",
            "answer" : "Saturn"
          },
          {
            "value": 400,
            "question" : "When will Halleys Comet return to Earth?",
            "answer" : "2061"
          },
          {
            "value": 600,
            "question" : "How much does a full NASA spacesuit cost (approximately)?",
            "answer" : "$12,000,000"
          },
          {
            "value": 800,
            "question" : "What was the number of the last Apollo mission?",
            "answer" : "17"
          },
          {
            "value": 1000,
            "question" : "How many known moons orbit Neptune?",
            "answer" : "14"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "name": "Hockey",
        "questions": [
          {
            "value": 200,
            "question" : "Which NHL player has the most career points?",
            "answer" : "Wayne Gretzky"
          },
          {
            "value": 400,
            "question" : "Who is the winningest NHL goalie of all time",
            "answer" : "Martain Brodeur"
          },
          {
            "value": 600,
            "question" : "What is the term for a goal, an assist, and a fight in one game?",
            "answer" : "Gordie Howe Hat Trick"
          },
          {
            "value": 800,
            "question" : "Who shot the fastest puck in recorded history?",
            "answer" : "Bobby Hull (rec. 118.3 mph)"
          },
          {
            "value": 1000,
            "question" : "Which NHL player holds the record for the most points in a single game?",
            "answer" : "Darryl Sittler"
          }
        ]
      }

    ]
  },
  "round2": {
    "categories": [
      {
        "name": "Lakes & Rivers",
        "questions": [
          {
            "value": 200,
            "question" : "What is the river most often mentioned in the bible?",
            "answer" : "The Jordan"
          },
          {
            "value": 400,
            "question" : "What is the Scottish word for Lake?",
            "answer" : "Loch"
          },
          {
            "value": 600,
            "question" : "Which American river is only 30 miles shorter than the Mississippi?",
            "answer" : "The Missouri River"
          },
          {
            "value": 800,
            "question" : "What is the World's largest lake",
            "answer" : "The Caspian Sea"
          },
          {
            "value": 1000,
            "question" : "What is the longest river in the word?",
            "answer" : "The Nile"
          }
        ]
      }
    ]
  }
}

